We'll be right back.
Smash the wave!
Luffy and Zoro use the strongest combo!
Hey, you there!
Yes, Captain T-Bone.
How did you get that injury on your arm?
Huh?
Oh, this?
I got bitten by a bug earlier and it bled when I scratched it.
How awful!
We must staunch the bleeding.
We'll have to make do with this.
Sir, you don't have to tear your cape just for me.
It may be your arm that's bleeding, but when one of my men is injured, it's my heart that hurts the most.
Captain, thank you.
Let us fill today and every day forth with good deeds so that peace and kindness shall reign.
This race is still really scary.
Captain!
I'll help!
Oh, good, but let me explain the problem first.
If there's anything I can do, even if it kills me, I will protect you.
Oh, thanks.
But the problem is with the officials at Car 6 and 7.
They were completely wiped out.
Not only that, the two criminals detained in Car 6 are missing.
That's awful!
We can't tell if the prisoners escaped on their own or if they were helped by an unknown intruder.
For heaven's sake, man, start a rescue operation.
Help the injured and spread the word to the other cars.
Yes, sir.
Nami.
Nami, can you hear me?
Yeah, what's going on, Sanji?
I've got some bad news.
Things have gotten complicated.
What do you mean?
Hey, wait a sec.
What was that noise?
Is someone there with you or something?
It's nothing.
Just some dumbass.
Huh?
Say what?
Sanji, what's that noise?
Sounds like a bunch of screaming.
Are you okay over there?
What do you mean by dumbass?
Sorry.
Dumbass is, actually.
Jimmy Cannon!
Leave it to us!
Not even making a dent.
I should have figured.
You think those puny things are gonna work?
Everybody step back!
Let the Frankie family special cannon do its stuff!
Target! Aqua Laguna!
Go! Super Scruff cannon fire!
Fire again! Don't land up!
Bring more cannonballs!
Got it! Aim at the center! Focus on one spot!
Focus, focus! Give it all you got!
Yeah, good luck with that!
By the way, the tracks do rise up a bit.
But not enough to get us over that wave.
Rocket Man has done pretty well out here so far.
But if we get hit, we're finished.
Does that mean we're all gonna die?
No guarantees! I warned you now, didn't I?
What? I don't wanna die!
I see. They still have Robin.
Yeah!
Sounds like things are pretty lively on your end, too.
Hey, listen, Sanjay.
Yeah!
I need to tell you why Robin's doing all this.
And also why everyone's screaming for that matter.
Shut up!
So like I was just saying, we found out why Robin's with CP9.
We're out here trying to follow her, but things are kind of crazy right now.
It's a long story.
We're all gonna die!
But I don't wanna die!
Me either!
If you have time to cry, keep firing!
We'll find a way out!
Hey, Luffy.
Yeah, I know what you're thinking.
That wave's asking for it, huh?
Come on! Keep those cannons firing!
What are you guys planning on doing?
Same thing as you.
What?
Hey, how much is 108 times two?
216.
216, huh?
That's too long!
Can't we round up or something?
Fine.
Make it 300, then.
I don't get it.
What do they think they're doing?
If cannons don't work, what could our swords gonna do?
Well, they did say we should keep fighting, though.
Stop yapping and back them up!
Roger!
Okay.
Ready?
Uh-huh.
Go, go, go!
300 caliber!
Big on the crash!
Stop!
Okay, I'm here for all the ps babysitters of so smokeiest time!
Governor!
Okay! Ready?
Uh-huh.
Now go, go!
Three hundred caliper!
Birdrun crash!
Target!
Whoa!
Come on, Tinko!
It's all or nothing.
We missed, Mom!
Let's go away!
Yeah!
Correct!
Okay.
AVAILABLE NOW
I'm not afraid of anything anymore!
Wow, that was really fun!
I knew you were strong, but that was something else!
Are you an alien or something? Because that was totally out of this world!
Oops, sorry about that.
Luffy, come here a sec!
Huh? Huh?
Sanji wants to talk.
That you, Luffy?
Yep, it's me!
What's up? You saved Robin?
No, sorry. I'm afraid I'm still working on that one.
Nami just told me why Robin surrendered and all of that stuff.
So, yeah, I know what's going on.
I see. That's good.
Well, anyway, you know what's next.
Go ahead. Give him hell, Sanji. Huh?
Hold on. He'll die if he fights them now.
If he wants to stand a chance, he's gotta wait for us.
Hey, Cook, can you hear me?
Some of the guys on that train are really tough. You should...
It's fine.
.
何度も何度も立ち止まりながら 笑顔と涙を積み重ねてゆく
どんなに闇の深い夜でも 必ず明日は来るから
We'll now begin Operation Rescue Robin.
Wait, Sanji! Don't you want to learn more about me first?
Before anything else, we gotta clear out the enemy forces.
Like my origin story or super moves?
We'll start with the weak guys, then work our way up.
Sniper King, I'll do my best!
Hey, would you shut up and listen to me?
Uh, yes, sir, sorry.
On the next, One Piece, a mysterious man appears?
His name is Sniper King!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!